<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1 | </title>
    <link>https://JosephChenHub.github.io/publication-type/1/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://JosephChenHub.github.io/publication-type/1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>1</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://JosephChenHub.github.io/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>https://JosephChenHub.github.io/publication-type/1/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Partial Rank Aggregation for Personalized Attributes</title>
      <link>https://JosephChenHub.github.io/publication/aaai21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://JosephChenHub.github.io/publication/aaai21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:
In this paper, we study the problem of how to aggregate pair-
wise personalized attributes (PA) annotations (e.g., Shoes A
is more comfortable than B) from different annotators on the
crowdsourcing platforms, which is an emerging topic gaining
increasing attention in recent years. Given the crowdsourced
annotations, the majority of the traditional literature assumes
that all the pairs in the collected dataset are distinguishable.
However, this assumption is incompatible with how humans
perceive attributes since indistinguishable pairs are ubiqui-
tous for the annotators due to the limitation of human percep-
tion. To attack this problem, we propose a novel deep pre-
diction model that could simultaneously detect the indistin-
guishable pairs and aggregate ranking results for distinguish-
able pairs. First of all, we represent the pairwise annotations
as a multi-graph. Based on such data structure, we propose
an end-to-end partial ranking model which consists of a deep
backbone architecture and a probabilistic model that captures
the generative process of the partial rank annotations. Specif-
ically, to recognize the indistinguishable pairs, the probabilis-
tic model we proposed is equipped with an adaptive percep-
tion threshold, where indistinguishable pairs could be auto-
matically detected when the absolute value of the score dif-
ference is below the learned threshold. In our empirical stud-
ies, we perform a series of experiments on three real-world
datasets: LFW-10, Shoes, and Sun. The corresponding results
consistently show the superiority of our proposed model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mainmainpng&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;main.png&#34; alt=&#34;main&#34;&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
 &lt;img src=&#34;main.png&#34; /&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Context-Aware Progressive Aggregation Network for Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://JosephChenHub.github.io/publication/aaai20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://JosephChenHub.github.io/publication/aaai20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;:
Deep convolutional neural networks have achieved competitive performance in salient object detection, in which how to learn effective and comprehensive features plays a critical role. Most of the previous works mainly adopted multiple-level feature integration yet ignored the gap between different features. Besides, there also exists a dilution process of high-level features as they passed on the top-down pathway. To remedy these issues, we propose a novel network named GCPANet to
effectively integrate low-level appearance features, high-level semantic features, and global context features through some progressive context-aware Feature Interweaved Aggregation (FIA) modules and generate the saliency map in a supervised way. Moreover, a Head Attention (HA) module is used to reduce information redundancy and enhance the top layers features by leveraging the spatial and channel-wise attention, and the Self Refinement (SR) module is utilized to further refine
and heighten the input features. Furthermore, we design the Global Context Flow (GCF) module to generate the global context information at different stages, which aims to learn the relationship among different salient regions and alleviate the dilution effect of high-level features. Experimental results on six benchmark datasets demonstrate that the proposed approach outperforms the state-of-the-art methods both quantitatively and qualitatively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;main.png&#34; alt=&#34;main&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;vis.png&#34; alt=&#34;vis&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
